University of Illinois Collection of Police Agreements and Arbitration Files 6334
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
University of Illinois Collection of Police Agreements and Arbitration Files
1968- 1986
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
University of Illinois
Smith, Becky
6334
18 cubic feet
18 linear ft.
Records.
7607098
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 17, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 27, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Collective labor agreements; University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign
7607098
- Birmingham, AL - Los Angeles, CA (Box 1)
  - Birmingham, Alabama 6 agreements 1976-1982 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Anchorage, AK 1 arbitration and 1979 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Anchorage, Alsaka 4 agreements 1974-82, 1974-1982 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Fairbanks, Alaska 5agreements 1974-82, 1974-1982 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Phoenix, Arizona 5 agreements 1977-82 time period, 1977-1982 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Tucson, Arizona 2 advisory arbitration awards (75+81), 1975-1981 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Tucson, Arizona 2 agreements 77-80 80-83, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - North Little Rock, Arkansas 1 agreement 1981-1983 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Alhambra, CA 6 agreements 1975-82, 1975-1982 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Anaheim, California 3 agreements 1975-83, 1975-1983 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Arcadia, CA 4 agreement 1975-83, 1975-1983 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Bakersfield, California 4 agreements 1977-82, 1977-1982 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Baldwin Park, California 1 agreement 81-83, 1981-1983 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Belmont, CA 4 agreement 1975-83, 1975-1983 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Berkeley, California 8 agreement 1970-84, 1970-1984 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Beverly Hills, California 4 memoranda of Understanding 1974-1983 period (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Brea, California 3 agreements 75-82, 1975-1982 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Burbank, California 5 agreements; 1975-83, 1975-1983 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Burlingame, California 3 agreements 1973-76; 1978-82, 1973-1982 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Campbell, California 4 agreements 1974-82, 1974-1982 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Chino, CA 4 agreements 1975-78; 1980-82, 1975-1982 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Chula Vista CA 6 agreements 75-82 (They didn't have a 77-78 agreement), 1978-1981 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Claremont, CA 4 agreements 76-82, 1976-1982 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Compton, California 3 agreements 1974-82, 1974-1982 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Concord, California 3 patrol agreements 1975-1981 1 managerial agreement 1981 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Corona, CA 6 agreements 74-82, 1974-1982 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Costa Mesa, CA 5 agreements 75-82, 1975-1982 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Covina, CA 5 agreements 76-83, 1976-1983 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Culver City, California 3 memoranda 1976-84 period., 1976-1984 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Cypress, CA 5 agreements 1974-83, 1974-1983 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Daly City, CA 6 agreements 1975-84, 1975-1984 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Davis CA 5 agreements 75-83, 1975-1983 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - El Cajon, California 7 memoranda 1975-82, 1975-1982 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - El Cerrito, CA 8 agreements 1974-82, 1974-1982 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Escondido, CA 5 agreements 74-83, 1974-1983 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Eureka, CA 1 agreement 80-83, 1980-1983 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Fountain Valley, California 3 agreements 1975-81, 1975-1981 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Fremont, California 2 agreements 1980-84, 1980-1984 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Fresno, California 2 agreements 1974-82, 1974-1982 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Fullerton, California 5 memoranda 1975-82, 1975-1982 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Garden Grove, CA 4 agreements 75-82, 1975-1982 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Gardena, CA 3 agreement 75-78; 79-83 extra copy 81-83 agreement, 1975-1983 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Hayward, CA X 6 agreements 75-83, 1975-1983 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Huntington Beach, California 1 agreement 81-83 (2 copies), 1981-1983 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Huntington Park, California 3 agreements 77-83, 1977-1983 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Inglewood, CA 4 agreements 1974-83, 1974-1983 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - La Habra, CA 6 agreements 1975-82, 1975-1982 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Livermore, California 4 memoranda 1975-1981 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Lodi, California 3 agreements 1974-81, 1974-1981 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Lompoc, CA 3 agreements 1974-83, 1974-1983 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Long Beach, California 1975 4 agreements Followup (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Los Angeles, California 1975 7 agreements (Box 1, Folder 52)
- Manhattan Beach, CA - Torrance, CA (Box 2)
  - Manhattan Beach, California 4 agreements: 1975-1985 1 extra copy of 81-85 agreement, 1975-1981 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Menlo Park, CA 3 offer agreemets 78-81 3 spnsr agreements 78-83, 1978-1983 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Merced, California 74 5 agreements 74-81, 1974-1981 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Modesto, California 5 agreements 1973-86, 1973-1986 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Monterey, CA 6 agreements 71-83, 1971-1983 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Monterey Park, CA 3 agreements 75-79, 1975-1979 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Mountain View, CA 6 agreements 1973-1983 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - 5 agreements 75-80, 1975-1980 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - 1 agreement 79-82, 1979-1982 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Oakland, California 1 agreement 81-82, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Orange, California 4 agreements 75-79; 80-82, 1975-1982 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Oxnard, California 4 memoranda 1975-83 period, 1975-1983 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Pacifica, CA B agreements 1975-81, 1975-1981 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Palm Springs, California 4 memoranda, 1976-1982 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Palo Alto, CA 3 agreements 72-82, 1972-1982 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Palo Alto, CA 1 arbitration award 1980 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Oceanside, California 1980-82 agreement., 1980-1982 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Pasadena, California 5 agreements 1973-82, 1973-1982 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Petaluma, CA 7 agreements 75-82, 1975-1982 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Placentia, CA 3 agreements 73-82, 1973-1982 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Pleasant Hill, CA 4 agreements 1974-82, 1974-1982 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Pleasanton, CA 4 agreements 1977-83, 1977-1983 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Redding, California 1 agreement 1974-82, 1974-1982 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Redondo Beach, CA 5 agreements 1975-82, 1975-1982 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Rialto, California 6 agreements 1972-85, 1972-1985 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Richmond, California 3 agreements 1976-78; 1979-81 (1981-83 agreement - 1 extra copy) They didn't have a 79-80 agreement, 1976- 1983 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Sacramento, California 6 agreements 1974-82, 1974-1982 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Salinas, California 6 agreements 1975-82, 1975-1982 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - County of San Bernardina, CA 4 agreements 1977-83 Not coded, 1977-1983 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - County of San Bernardino, CA 1 advisory arbitration Award 1980 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - San Bernardino. California 1 agreement 1981-82, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - San Bruno, California 1981-83-agreement., 1981-1983 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - San Buenaventura (ventura) CA 4 agreements 75-82 Mgmt. Agreemt., 1975-1982 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - San Diego, California 2 agreements 1980-82, 1980-1982 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - San Carlos, CA 5 agreements 1975-83, 1975-1983 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - San Gabriel, California 7 memoranda 1975-82, 1975-1982 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - San Jose, California 1 agreement 1981-83, 1981-1983 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - San Leandro, California 6 agreements 1974-83, 1974-1983 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - San Luis Obispo, California 5 agreements 74-82, 1974-1982 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - San Mateo, California 1 agreements 74-83, 1974-1983 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - San Rafael, CA 2 agreements 1976-82, 1976-1982 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Santa Ana, California 1 agreement 1981-83, 1981-1983 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Santa Clara, California 1976-84 agreements., 1976-1984 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Santa Cruz, CA 5 agreements 75-82, 1975-1982 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Santa Maria, California 4 agreements. 1974-84, 1974-1984 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Santa Monica, CA 5 agreements. 1975-85, 1975-1985 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Santa Rosa, California 2 agreements: Police offers 81-83 Police spusrs 81-83, 1981-1983 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Simi Valley, California 6 agreements 1974-83, 1974-1983 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - South San Francisco, California 4 agreements 1975-82, 1975-1982 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Stockton, CA 5 agreements. 75-83 1 extra copy of 80-83, 1975-1983 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Sunnyvale, CA 3 agreements 74-79, 1974-1979 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Terrance, CA 4 agreements 1975-82, 1975-1982 (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Tustin, CA - Southington, CT (Box 3)
  - Tustin, California 3 memoranda 1976, 1977, 1980-82, 1976-1982 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Union City, CA 5 agreements 75-81, 1975-1981 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Upland, CA 7 agreements 75-81, 1975-1981 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Vallejo, CA 3 agreements of 4 amendments 1975-82, 1975-1982 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Visalia, California changes in agreement. For 1981-82, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Walnut Creek, CA 7 agreements 1975-82, 1975-1982 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - West Covina, California 7 agreements 74-81, 1974-1981 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Whittier, California 5 agreements 74-75; 76-83, 1974-1983 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Woodland, California 5 agreements 1975-82, 1975-1982 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Aurora, Colorado V 2 agreements 1979-82 1 IAFF agreement 1 extra police 81-82 agreement., 1979-1982 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Boulder, Colorado 6 agreements. 1975-83, 1975-1983 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Englewood Colorado 3 Memoranda 1975-79 1 contract 1980-81, 1975-1981 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Greeley, Colorado 1 agreement 1982-83 (2 copies), 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Littleton, Colorado 6 agreements 1975-82, 1975-1982 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Pueblo, Colorado 1 agreement 82-83, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Bridgeport, Connecticut 3 agreements 1974-1982 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Bristol, CT 2 agreements 77-83, 1977-1983 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - East Hartford, Connecticut 3 agreements. 1976-82, 1976-1982 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Enfield, Connecticut 4 agreements 1973-82, 1973-1982 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Enfield, Connecticut 1 award for 78 agreement., 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Greenwich, Connecticut 3 agreements.. 1975-81, 1975-1981 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Greenwich, Connecticut larbitration award 1978 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Groton, CT 4 agreements. 1973-83, 1973-1983 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Hamden, Connecticut 3 agreements. 1972-81, 1972-1981 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Hartford, Connecticut 3 agreements. 1975-84 period, 1975-1984 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Manchester, Connecticut 1974-80 period 3 agreements., 1974-1980 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Meriden, Connecticut 4 agreements. 1975-82 period, 1975-1982 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Meridan, CT larbitration award 1976 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Middletown, CT 1 award for 7/76-6/78, 1976-1978 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Milford, Connecticut (1 agreement 80-82), 1980-1982 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - New Britain, CT 1 award for 7/76-6/78, 1976-1978 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - New Haven, CT 1 award for 7/76-6/78, 1976-1978 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - New London, CT 2 arbitration Awards for 10/77-6/80 9/82-6/84, 1977-1984 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Newington, Connecticut 3 agreements 1975-83 1 extra copy of 81-83 agreement., 1975-1983 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Norwalk, Connecticut 3 agreements 1972-1981 period (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Norwich, CT. 4 agreements 75-84 2 FF reports 78+81, 1975-1984 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Southington, CT 2 arbitration awards. 1977-1982 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Southington, CT 2 agreement. 1979-83, 1979-1983 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Stamford, CT - Miramar, FL (Box 4)
  - Stamford, Connecticut 3 agreements. 1974-1981 Time Period (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Trumball, CT 1 agreement 80-83 cb since 71, 1971-1983 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Wallingford, Connecticut 2 agreements. 1976-82, 1976-1982 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Waterbury, CT larbitration Award for 1/78-6/79, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - West Hartford, Connecticut 1 agreement. 1981-83, 1981-1983 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Wethersfield, CT 1 arbitration Award for 7/76-6/78, 1976-1978 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Newark, Delaware 4 agreements. 1974-82 period, 1974-1982 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Wilmington, Delaware 4 agreements 1974-1983 period (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Wilmington, Delaware 4 agreements. 1974-1983 period (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Washington, D.C. 3 agreements 1975-84, 1975-1984 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Boca Raton, FL 5 agreements. 1975-83, 1975-1983 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Clearwater, Florida 5 agreements. 1974-1984 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Coral Gables, FL 1 agreement 81-82, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Deerfield Beach, FL 2 IAFF agreements., 1977 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Deerfield Beach, Florida 1 special Master Report 1977 (similar to FF) (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Deerfield Beach, Florida 6 agreements 1977-1983 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Fort Myers, Florida 5 agreements Followup, 1977-1982 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Fat Pierce, Florida 3 agreements 1979-82, 1979-1982 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Gainesville, Florida 3 agreement. 77-82, 1977-1982 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Haleah, FL 5 agreements 1975-82, 1975-1982 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Hollywood, FL 1 agreement 80-82, 1980-1982 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Jacksonville, Florida 1973-75 3 patrol agreement. 77-83 1 it. + capt. agreement. 81-83, 1977-1983 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Largo, Florida 1 agreement 1981-83, 1981-1983 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Margate, Florida 4 agreements. 1976-82, 1976-1982 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Melbourne, Florida 5 agreements. 1975-82, 1975-1982 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Miami, Florida 3 agreements. 1974-81, 1974-1981 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Miami Beach, FL 3 agreements. 1974-82, 1974-1982 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Miramar, Florida 1 agreement. 1980-82, 1980-1982 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- North Miami, FL - Elgin, IL (Box 5)
  - North Miami, Florida 5 agreements 1977-82, 1977-1982 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - North Miami Beach, FL 1 Special Master Report, 1977 1 FL Sup. Ct. Decision (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - North Miami Beach, Florida 1 agreement. 1981-83, 1981-1983 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Orlando, FL 3 agreements. 1977-83, 1977-1983 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Pinellas Park, FL 1 agreement. 1981-1983 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Riviera Beach, Florida 5 agreements 1975-82, 1975-1982 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Sarasota, Florida 4 agreements 1976-81, 1976-1981 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - St Petersburg, Florida 2 Special Master Reports, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - St. Petersburg, Florida 5 agreements; 1975-83, 1975-1983 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Sunrise, Florida 1 agreement. 1979-82, 1979-1982 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Tallahassee, Florida 3 agreements. 1974-82 period, 1974-1982 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Tallahassee, Florida ispecial master decision, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Tamaras, Florida 1978-82 agreements (3 agreements), 1978-1982 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Tampa, Florida 2 agreements. 1976-1982 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Honolulu, Hawaii 4 agreements 1979-83, 1979-1983 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Boise, Idaho 7 agreements 1975-1982 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Aurora, Illinois 4 agreement 1975-83, 1975-1983 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Belleville, Illinois 3 agreements. 1975-77-79-80; 80-82, 1975-1982 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Berwyn, Il 2 agreements. 74-75, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Bloomington, Illinois agreements. 1974-83, 1974-1983 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Carbitrationondale, Illinois 3agreements 1976-82, 1976-1982 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Carpentersville, Illinois 3 agreements. 1978-82, 1978-1982 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Champaign, Illinois 4 agreements. 1974-83, 1974-1983 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Chicago, Illinois (1981-83 contract), 1981-1983 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Danville, Illinois 1 agreement. 1982-84, 1982-1984 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Dekalb, Illinois 5 agreements. 1970-73 1975-83, 1970-1983 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Decatur, Illinois 4 agreements. 1976-83, 1976-1983 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Des Plaines, Illinois 4 agreements. 1975-78; 1980-83, 1975-1983 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - East St. Louis, IL 1 agreement. 1980 language serves for 75-81 period, 1975-1981 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Elgin, IL 4 agreements. 1974-81, 1974-1981 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Evanston, IL - Iowa City, IA (Box 6)
  - Evanston, Illinois 7 agreements. 1974-82 1 extra copy of 81-82 agreement., 1974-1982 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Galesburg, Illinois 8 agreements 1971-81, 1971-1981 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Harvey, Illinois 1 agreement. 1980-81, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Harvey, Illinois 1 agreement. 1980-81, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Hoffman Estates, Illinois 1 agreement. 1981-83, 1981-1983 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Joliet, Illinois 9 agreements: 5 patrolmen agreements (AFSCME) 1976-84, 1976-1984 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Kankakee, Illinois 1 agreement. 1979-82, 1979-1982 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Maywood, Illinois 1 agreement. 80-82, 1980-1982 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Moline, Illinois 4 agreements 1974-1982 1 copy of group benefits plan 1 extra copy of 80-82 agreement. (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Haperville, Illinois 1 agreement. 1976-77, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Northbrook, Illinois 3 agreements. 1974-83, 1974-1983 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Oak Part, Illinois 1 agreement 1980-81, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Park Ridge, Illinois 3 agreements 1975-81, 1975-1981 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Quincy, Illinois 4 agreements. 1976-82, 1976-1982 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Springfield, Illinois 3 agreements. 1975-83, 1975-1983 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Urbana, Illinois 4 agreements. 1975-82 and 1 extra copy of 80-82, 1975-1982 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Bloomington, Indiana 2 agreements. 1979-84, 1979-1984 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Elkhart, Indiana 1 agreement. Cal yr 1981 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Evansville, Indiana 5 agreements. 1977-82, 1977-1982 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Fort Wayne, Indiana 2 local arbitration Awards 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Indianapolis, In 59 agreements. 1974-82, 1974-1982 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Kokomo, In 1 agreement. 81-82, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Marion, Indiana 4 agreement. 1978-1981 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Michigan City, In 4 agreements. 1979-82, 1979-1982 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Muncie, In 3 agreements. 1978-84, 1978-1984 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - New Albany, IN 1 agreement 78-79, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Richmond, In 6 agreements. 1975-81, 1975-1981 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Terre Hawte, In 1 agreement 82-83, 1982-1983 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Ames, IA, 1977-1979 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Burlington, Iowa 3 agreements 7/77-6/80, 1977-1980 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Cedar Falls, IA, 1977-1981 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Cedar Falls, IA 2 arbitration Awards for 7/77-6/78 7/81-6/82, 1977-1982 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Cedar Rapids, IA 2 arbitration Awards for 7/76-6/77 7/77-6/78, 1976-1978 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Cedar Rapids, Iowa 1 agreement. 1981-82, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Clinton, Iowa 5 agreements 1976-83, 1976-1983 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Council Bluffs, Iowa 4 agreements 1975-82, 1975-1982 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Council Bluffs, Iowa 2 arbitration Awards for 78-79 79-80 agreements., 1978-1980 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Davenport, IA 1 arbitration Award for 7/77-6/78, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Davenport, Iowa 5(sent 3 agreements 1977-84) have used arbitration Did not send award., 1977-1984 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Des Moines, Iowa 1 arbitration Award 1981 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Des Moines, Iowa (1 agreements: 1981-82), 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Dubuque, Iowa 5 agreements. 1975-82, 1975-1982 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Dubuque, Iowa 2 arbitration 1977; 1981 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Fort Dodge, IA, 1976-1979 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Fort Dodge, IA 1 arbitration Award for 7/77-6/78, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Iowa City, Iowa 1. arbitration award for 1980-81, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 46)
- Marshalltown, IA - Fall River, MA (Box 7)
  - Marshall town, Iowa 2 agreement. 1979-84, 1979-1984 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Marshalltown, IA 1 arbitration And 1980 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Mason City, IA, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Mason City, IA 2 arbitration awards. 79-80/ 80-81, 1979-1981 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Ottumwa, IA, 1977-1979 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Sioux City, Iowa 2 arbitration awards 1977;1978 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Sioux City, Iowa 4 agreements 1977-83 period, 1977-1983 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Waterloo, Iowa (1 extra copy of 79-82 B agreement. 1976-82, 1976-1982 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Agreement Between the City of West Des Moines, Iowa and Local 55 of the Iowa State Policemen's Association, 1979-1981 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Lawrence, KC 4 agreements 77-82, 1977-1982 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Topeka, Kansas 3 agreements (1976-84 time period), 1976-1984 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Covington, Kentucky 4 agreements, 1975-82, 1975-1982 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Jefferson County (Louisville), KY 5 agreements. 1975-83 extra copy of 81-83, 1975-1983 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Alexandria, Louisiana 1 agreement. 1977-87 (only agreement.), 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Monroe, Louisiana 8 agreements. 1974-82, 1974-1982 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Bangor, Maine 1 agreement. 1980-81, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Kittery, Maine, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Portland, Maine 4 agreements 1974-82, 1974-1982 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Cumberland, Maryland sent 4 agreements 1975-82, 1975-1982 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Hagerstown, Maryland 2 agreements 1977-81, 1977-1981 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Amherst, MA 1 arbitration Award for 7/80-6/82 period, 1980-1982 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Amherst, Ma. 1 agreement. 82-83, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Andover, MA 2 agreements 7/76-6/80, 1976-1980 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Arlington, MA. Changes in 1 agreement. 7/75-6/76, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Attleboro, MA 4 agreements 1974-80 1982-84; The 1980-82 agreement. is an arbitration and in the arbitration. File, 1974-1984 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Attleboro Massachusetts 1 arbitration award. 1980 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Barnstable, MA 4 agreements. 7/76-6/83, 1976-1983 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Belmont, MA 1 agreement. 7/76-6/78, 1976-1978 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Belmont, Massachusetts 1 agreement. 7/80-6/82, 1980-1982 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Beverly, MA 3 agreements 1/76-6/82, 1976-1982 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Bitterica, MA 3 agreements. 68-69; 75-83, 1968-1983 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Billerica, MA 1 arbitration Award for 7/78-6/80, 1978-1980 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Boston, MA 7 agreements 1/68-6/81, 1968-1981 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Boston, MA 2 arbitration Awards for 7/74-6/75, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Braintree, Massachusetts 2 agreements patrolmen spnsrs. 1980-83 1981-84, 1980-1984 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Brookline, MA 1 agreement. 81-82 1 agreement. 77-78, 1977-1982 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Cambridge, MA 4 agreements 73-81, 1973-1981 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Chelmsford, Massachusetts 3 agreement 1976-82, 1976-1982 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Chelsea, MA 1 arbitration Award for 7/78-6/80, 1978-1980 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Chicopee, MA 100 agreements: 6 ofer 4 sausr 71-74;77-83, 1971-1983 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Fall River, MA 1 agreement. 7/78-6/81, 1978-1981 (Box 7, Folder 43)
- Fitchburg, MA - Battle Creek, MI (Box 8)
  - Pitchburg, MA 1 agreement 80-82, 1980-1982 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Framingham, Massachusetts 3 agreements 1976-1983 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Framingham, MA 1 arbitration award for 7/80-6/83 period, 1980-1983 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Gloucester, MA 1 arbitration Award for 7/76-6/79, 1976-1979 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Gloucester, MA 1 agreement. (changes only) 7/79-6/81 - 1 agreement in arbitration Award form in award files, 1979-1981 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Haverhill, Massachusetts 1 agreement. 80-83, 1980-1983 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Holyoke, MA 2 agreements 1/77-6/78, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 7)